Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.17
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Ongoing Career, 1993; XVII.
  - Events, 4.
    - New Material Added, August 2018
      - Interview with Jonathan Lomma for The American Jurist, student magazine for American University's College of Law, October 10, 2001 (Box 1061, Folder 63)
      - IIFWP's Assembly 2001 on "Global Violence: Crisis and Hope": Remarks "What Role for the U.N. in the War Against Terrorism", New York, October 21, 2001 (Box 1061, Folder 64)
      - Business Council Meeting: Panel topic "What is the nature of the ongoing threat to U.S. Interests?", October 26, 2001 (Box 1061, Folder 65)
      - K&L Virtual Retreat, October 26, 2001 (Box 1061, Folder 66)
      - Patriot Series Award Presentation, October 30, 2001 (Box 1061, Folder 67)
      - American Iron and Steel Institute, October 31, 2001 (Box 1061, Folder 68)
      - Meeting with Bethlehem Steel executive, December 11, 2001 (Box 1061, Folder 69)
      - Corporate Legal Times Roundtable sponsored by K&L, December 13, 2001 (Box 1061, Folder 70)
      - Video interview re: OCDETF 20th anniversary, July 9, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 71)
      - Meeting Kenneth Wollensky re: his book of Pennsylvania's 20th century governors, July 18, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 72)
      - ADA Celebration with House Bipartisan Disability Caucus, July 24, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 73)
      - Memorial Service to Honor Justin Dart, Jr., July 26, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 74)
      - NHK JPA-TV Interview, re: Information Technology & our Society (Japanese Broadcasting Corporation), August 12, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 75)
      - Videotaping Message re: Shel Parker's retirement, September 9, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 76)
      - Council on Foreign Relations Meeting, September 18, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 77)
      - International Disability Award to Representative of Ecuador at UN, September 19, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 78)
      - Meeting with Andrew Hale-Byrne et al, re: ADA, September 17, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 79)
      - Chestnut Hill Presbyterian Church Religion & Disability Issues Speaking, September 22, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 80)
      - Brooks Smith Swearing in Ceremony as US Court of Appeals, Third Circuit, Pittsburgh, September 23, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 81)
      - National Day Reception at Saudi Arabia Embassy, September 23, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 82)
      - BBVA Paul Maarttila Meeting, September 24, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 83)
      - Meeting, re. Sudan (terrorism), September 30, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 84)
      - Charles G. Watson Surgical Education Center Opening and Portrait Unveiling, October 16, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 85)
      - Children's Institute 100th Anniversary Celebration, October 17, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 86)
      - Yale Engineering School Alumni Reunion & Panel Program, October 18-20, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 87)
      - Longwood at Oakmont Dinner, October 30,2002 (Box 1061, Folder 88)
      - Washington Lions Club 75th Anniversary, October 31, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 89)
      - Pitt 2002 Distinguished Alumni Award Dinner, November 2, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 90)
      - Videotaping of Message for PennDot 100th Anniversary, November 14, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 91)
      - International Society for the Reform of Criminal Law Conference, Charleston, SC, December 6-10, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 92)
      - Meeting with Yakovlev and Russian delegation, postponed (Box 1061, Folder 93)
      - Pennsylvania Society Dinner, December 14, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 94)
      - All Africa Conference on Law, Justice & Development, December 17, 2002 (Box 1061, Folder 95)
      - New Year's Renaissance Weekend, Charleston, SC, December 28, 2002-January 1, 2003 (Box 1061, Folder 96)
      - Thomas Pomeroy, Jr. Memorial Service, January 4, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 1)
      - Center for Legal Policy, Manhattan Institute, January 14, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 2)
      - Council for Foreign Relations, January 15, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 3)
      - Meeting with Bill Gormley re: Attorney General years, February 10, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 4)
      - Council for Foreign Relations meeting with AG John Ashcroft, February 10, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 5)
      - Premier of Gods & Generals at National Theatre, February 10, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 6)
      - Anniversary Celebration of George Bush Presidential Library Center, February 11, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 7)
      - Breakfast Meeting with San Francisco Office Attorneys, February 28, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 8)
      - Attorneys General Forum, Hastings College of Law, February 27, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 9)
      - Ben Franklin Partners Champion Award to Thornburgh, March 3, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 10)
      - Henry Betts Award to Ginny and Dick Thornburgh, March 4, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 11)
      - The Chester Forum, Chester, Va.; Speech "Some Thoughts On America's Challenges At Home and Abroad: The Centrality of Democracy and the Rule of Law", March 8, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 12)
      - Interview with Harrisburg Magazine, Lisa Paige, March 10, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 13)
      - Meeting with Russian Judges, and Yakovlev, March 11, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 14)
      - Russian Judicial Delegation Visit; Center for Democracy, Open World Program at Library of Congress, March 12, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 15)
      - Washington-Lincoln-Reagan Day Dinner, Charlottesville, Speech "America Faces The Challenge of War At Home and Abroad", March 19, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 16)
      - Remarks of Dick Thornburgh at Funeral Mass for Matthew J. Ryan, Speaker of PA House of Representatives, April 3, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 17)
      - Salute to the Parks Association Dinner, April 9, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 19)
      - National Opening Ceremony of 15th Annual National Youth Service Day at Orr Elementary School, Washington, April 11, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 20)
      - American Bankruptcy Institute Plenary Session; Panel Moderator, April 11, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 21)
      - Purdue Series on Corporate, Citizenship and Ethics; Remarks "Crisis in Corporate America?', April 14, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 22)
      - Background information re above Purdue Remarks, April 14, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 23)
      - DC Court of Appeals Law Clerks Luncheon, April 21, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 24)
      - Commencement Address Grove City College, May 17, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 25)
      - CLO (Chief Legal Executive, LLC) Conference, Chicago; Remarks: "Dealing With the Crisis in Corporate America: The Lawyers' Role", June 2-3, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 26)
      - Welcoming Reception for Hong Kong Delegation; Hotel Tabard Inn, June 3, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 27)
      - Graduation Speech, Sewickley Academy, June 7, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 28)
      - Graduation Speech, Sewickley Academy, June 19, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 29)
      - Person to Person telephone interview with Matt Gerson re: Supreme Court, June 27, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 30)
      - Telephone Interview with Dan Eldridge of Piit Magazine re: funding Thornburgh Family Lecture Series, July 1, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 31)
      - Meeting, Thornburgh Advisory Committee, July 7, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 32)
      - US Court/DC Law Clerks Luncheon, July 9, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 33)
      - ARC Florida 50th Annual Convention; Remarks: "Disabilities and Civil Rights: The Challenges of Empowerment", July 11, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 34)
      - Lunch with Korean Ambassador and Dr. Kang, July 23, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 35)
      - Meeting with Matt Forssan, July 24, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 36)
      - Meeting at International Municipal Lawyers Association (IMLA), July 25, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 37)
      - Telephone Interview with Jane Silk of Behind The Headlines/Radio America Program, August 15, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 38)
      - Interview with Candy Cushman of Focus on the Family, re: obscenity prosecutions, September 2, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 39)
      - Dinner with Ambassador of Taiwan C.J. Chenat Twin Oaks, September 2, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 40)
      - Dinner with Dick Dahling and wife Nancy, September 4, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 41)
      - Council on Foreign Relations General Meeting "What Future for the UN", September 11, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 42)
      - Fox/ The Big Story with Host Judge Napolitano: "Trial Lawyers", September 23, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 43)
      - Court TV/ The Catherine Crier Show "Trial Lawyers", September 23, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 44)
      - Trial Lawyers Inc. - A Report on the Lawsuit Industry in America, September 23, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 45)
      - Fox/Cal Thomas Show re Court TV: Trial Lawyers, September 24, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 46)
      - CNBC/Kudlow & Cramer Interview: Trial Lawyers, September 24, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 47)
      - WTAE/TV Interview, re: PA Turnpike, October 4, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 48)
      - Taping re: Pitt's 50Academic Reputation Video Spot: Top 2%, October 9, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 49)
      - Event: Faith, Ethics, and the Law; Princeton theological Seminary Center of Continuing Education; Remarks "Faith, Ethics and the Law", October 14-15, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 50)
      - Luncheon in support of Jim Roddey, Chief Executive Allegheny County, October 24, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 51)
      - Transatlantic Business Conference, in Pittsburgh, October 26, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 52)
      - National Association of Corporate Directors of Bay Area Program/San Francisco, October 28, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 53)
      - Princeton Survey Research Associates Telephone Call, November 5, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 54)
      - Dick Jewell Investiture Ceremonies, Grove City College, November 15, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 55)
      - Interview with Greg Milligan re PA Senator Jubelier tribute, November 19, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 56)
      - National Association of Corporate Directors Breakfast in Philadelphia, December 2, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 57)
      - SOX Book Reception in Pittsburgh, December 3, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 58)
      - ABA/Federal Regulation of Securities Program, Speech on Corporate Governance, Washington, DC, December 5, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 59)
      - Pennsylvania Society Dinner, December 13, 2003 (Box 1062, Folder 60)
      - University of Pittsburgh Board of Trustees Retreat, January 10, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 61)
      - University of Pittsburgh Board of Trustees Minutes, February 19, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 62)
      - University of Pittsburgh Board of Trustees Meeting, February 27, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 63)
      - CalTech Program on Issues in Government, Leadership, Technology & Social Trends, March 22, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 64)
      - Smithsonian National Museum of American History: Program on Three Mile Island, March 28, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 65)
      - Voice of America Interview, re: Three Mile Island, March 29, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 66)
      - Jepson School of Leadership Forum/University of Richmond, VA, March 30, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 67)
      - Bryce Harlow Foundation Annual Award Dinner Honoring George Koch /2004 Business Government Relations Award, March 31, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 68)
      - NOD reception to honor SOS (Start on Success) Program, at Library of Congress, April 15, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 69)
      - Meeting with Katherine Bertini, US Chief of Management at UN, April 22, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 70)
      - International Municipal Lawyers Association Speech, April 26, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 71)
      - Lunch with Dick Delonis, President of NAUSA, April 27, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 72)
      - Widener University/Omicron Delta Kappa Induction/Chartering Ceremonies, April 29, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 73)
      - Interview of Thornburghs by Irving Benig, May 1, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 74)
      - Jay Waldman Portrait Presentation (at Courthouse in Philadelphia), May 7, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 75)
      - Keynote Speaker/Corporate Counsel Forum 2004 aboard cruise ship: "Crisis in Corporate America? Some Lessons from WorldCom", May 13, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 76)
      - Meeting with Garry Hunter, IMLA President, May 14, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 77)
      - Interview, re: Michael Mead Video/Contributions, re: Bayfront Parkway in Erie, PA, May 18, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 78)
      - Community Resources for Independence/Award Presentation and Dinner, Santa Rosa, CA, May 22, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 79)
      - Yale 50th Reunion, June 3-6, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 80)
      - State Funeral of President Ronald Reagan at National Cathedral, June 11, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 81)
      - Dinner at British Embassy celebrating The Cabinet War Rooms in London, June 15, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 82)
      - Koch Industries Program, Aspen re: Lawsuit Abuse (with Jom Copeland, Manhattan Institute), June 28, 2004 (Box 1062, Folder 83)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: 2003 Supreme Court Term Review, June 30, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 1)
      - Meeting with Jeff Martin of Shea & Gardner and Prof. Warren Neal, re: Corporate Governance, July 7, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 2)
      - Volar Center for Independent Living, El Paso, Texas; Address "Our Lives, Our America: The Challenges of Empowerment and Self-Determination", July 23, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 3)
      - 2004 National Youth Leadership Network Conference, Arlington, VA, July 26, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 4)
      - Labor Day Renaissance Weekend, Monterey, CA, September 2-6, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 5)
      - Millersville University 150th Anniversary Celebration, September 9-10, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 6)
      - Luncheon, re: Inter-American Development Bank, September 17, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 7)
      - The Woodlands Butterfly Ball, Pittsburgh, September 18, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 8)
      - The People Speak Program re: American Power and Global Security, September 22, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 9)
      - Interview with Bill Flanagan re: book, career, PA economic situation in Pittsburgh, September 23, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 10)
      - Homeland Security Seminar-K&L offices in Pittsburgh, September 23, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 11)
      - Twentieth Century Club Program (in Pittsburgh), September 26, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 12)
      - Mississippians for Economic Progress, Jackson, Missippi, October 5, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 13)
      - Jumonville Sponsors Dinner; Remarks "The Role of Faith in Public Service", October 13, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 14)
      - First Thornburgh Disability Lecture; Speaker Peter Blanck: Americans with Disabilities and their Civil Rights for Employment", October 14, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 15)
      - Risk & Insurance Management Society Program; Remarks "Homeland Security and Your Business", October 19, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 16)
      - Atlantic Monthly Dinner in NYC, October 26, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 17)
      - Interview with Terrance Austin/World of Wonder & AMC, re: TMI & Impact of The China Syndrome, November 3, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 18)
      - Third Circuit Judicial Conference, Hershey, PA; Remarks, November 4, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 19)
      - Opening Kenneth E. Behring Hall of Military History: "The Price of Freedom: Americans at War; Smithsonian Institution", November 10, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 20)
      - Financial Executives Institute/Pittsburgh Chapter; Remarks "A Crisis in Corporate Governance?" The WorldCom Experience", November 9, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 21)
      - Jay Waldman Headstone Unveiling in Philadelphia, November 16, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 22)
      - Videotape of Birthday Message for Dr.House (March of Dimes) at National Press Club, November 16, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 23)
      - Adult Ed Issues Class/Georgetown Presbyterian Church: Remarks "The Role of Faith in Public Service", December 5, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 24)
      - Pennsylvania Society Dinner In New York, December 11, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 25)
      - Betts Award Jury Meeting at National Rehabilitation Hospital Board Room, December 14, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 26)
      - Trip to George Bush Library in Houston, TX, December 27, 2004 (Box 1063, Folder 27)
      - Board of Trustees, Princeton Theological Seminary, Naples, FL, January 16-18, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 28)
      - Yale Club Luncheon, Naples, FL, January 17, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 29)
      - President Bush's Oath of Office Ceremony Invitation, January 20, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 30)
      - Interview by Mike Bushnell, high school student, January 21, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 31)
      - Meeting with John Kemp & Stephen Bennett, re: "Big Sky Project" by United Cerebral Palsy, February 11, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 32)
      - Installation Ceremony for AG Alberto Gonzales at DOJ, February 14, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 33)
      - Meeting with Rod Hills & Dr. Feulner (of Heritage), February 15, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 34)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: 2003 Supreme Court Term Review, February 15, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 35)
      - Breakfast Meeting: Connie Larchner & Dan Popeo, February 15, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 36)
      - McLean Law Lecture, University of Pittsburgh; Speech: "The Global Effort to Contain Official Corruption", February 24, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 37)
      - Washington Rotary Club Luncheon; Thornburgh "notes", March 16, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 38)
      - University of Pittsburgh School of Law, Law Review Banquet; Speech "Homeland Security, Civil Liberties and The Rule of Law", April 8, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 39)
      - Meeting Mike Greco, ABA President-Elect, April 12, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 40)
      - International Academy of Trial Lawyers Annual Meeting; Speech: "Integrity in Investigative Journalism: Some Thoughts on the CBS News 'Sixty Minutes Wednesday' Inquiry", April 15, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 41)
      - Interview with Kyodo News Reporters: Tanigue and Yoneyama, re: TMI, April 18, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 42)
      - Pittsburgh Council for International Visitors/ 2005 International Bridge Award, April 23, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 43)
      - US Institute of Peace/Task Force on United Nations, April 25, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 44)
      - Hubert H. Humphrey Civil Rights Award to Ginny Thornburgh Event, May 4, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 45)
      - Fundraiser for Bill Green, candidate of district judge, Pittsburgh, May 6, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 46)
      - St. Vincent College Commencement Program; Speech by Dick Thornburgh, May 7, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 47)
      - Meeting with Nancy Baker of New Mexico State University, re: Hof Office of Attorney General has Evolved, May 11, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 48)
      - Reception Honoring publication of Book "To Preserve and Protect: The Life of Edwin Meese III", May 17, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 49)
      - Meeting with Bill Maynes at Eurasia Foundation re Rule of Law Project in Russia, May 19, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 50)
      - ILI/Roundtable Discussion with Russian Delegation of Judicial Reform Officials. Note earlier date but filed with previous item, July 17, 2003 (Box 1063, Folder 51)
      - Washington & Jefferson Graduation Speaker, May 21, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 52)
      - Leadership Harrisburg Area (LHA) Luncheon Series; Speech: "Some Thoughts on Leadership: 'Doing the Right Thing' and 'Doing the Thing Right'", June 1, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 53)
      - Taped Interview for Shippensburg University, re: Retirement of President Anthony Ceddia, June 1, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 54)
      - Interview with Dan Matson, Producer for Creative Differences, re: 666 Lottery case of 1980, June 7, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 55)
      - WLF Panel Discussion, re: "Assessing Arthur Andersen: what Did the Court Rule and How Will it Impact Criminal Enforcement?", June 9, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 56)
      - Council on Foreign Relations/HBO Screening & CFR Discussion of 'The Girl in the Café', June 22, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 57)
      - University of Pittsburgh Board of Trustees Event at home of Chancellor Nordenberg, June 23, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 58)
      - Meeting with Charles Bentz, re: Army Heritage Center Foundation, June 29, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 59)
      - Transatlantic Business Conference, re: Homeland Security (in London, England), July 12-14, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 60)
      - Council on Foreign Relations/HBO Screening & CFR Discussion of 'The Girl in the Café', July 14, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 61)
      - Internet radio show with Joyce Bender " Disability Matters", July 19, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 62)
      - Interview, re: 100th Anniversary of PA State Capitol, July 19, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 63)
      - Institute for Peace Forum, re: UN Management Reform (per Rod Hills), July 20, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 64)
      - Firmwide Videoconference, re: Collaboration with US/UK & Chinese counsel, July 21, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 65)
      - Christian Council of Korea (Young Woo Kang) Program, July 25, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 66)
      - National Council on Disability Reception, re: 15th Anniversary of ADA, July 25, 2005 (Box 1063, Folder 67)
      - Law Clerks' Speakers Program Luncheon at US Courthouse, July 28, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 1)
      - Documentary on Nate Smith, August 19, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 2)
      - Interview with Gerald & Deborah Strober, re: Oral Biography of Rudolph Giuliani, August 24, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 3)
      - Breakfast meeting with Glen Meakem, re: heading Scranton's campaign for Governor, August 26, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 4)
      - American Enterprise Institute Symposium, re: UN Reform (in DC), September 12, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 5)
      - Meeting with Jonathan Young, re: Stetson Disability Speech, September 13, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 6)
      - Stetson University College of Law Program, re: dedication of William R. Eleazer Courtroom, September 16, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 7)
      - Washington Legal Foundation meeting with Representatives of Murdock Trust, September 23, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 8)
      - World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh; Speech "Defining the United States Relationship with the United Nations in the 21st Century", September 27-28, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 9)
      - Corporate Counsel Symposium: Best Practices for Litigation Management; Remarks "Internal Corporate Investigations", September 29, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 10)
      - Meeting with Mark Dion & Matt Leonardo, re: Hill Scranton Campaign, October 4, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 11)
      - Investiture of John Roberts as Chief Justice of the Supreme Court, October 3, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 12)
      - CNN/Wolf Blitzer, re: Harriet Miers/Supreme Court & Cases discussed this week, October 9, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 13)
      - Pittsburgh Urban Magnet Project (PUMP), October 14, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 14)
      - Navy League of Pittsburgh/20th Anniversary of USS Pittsburgh, October 14, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 15)
      - Penn State Forum Speakers Luncheon, Nittany Lion Inn, October 17, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 16)
      - WPSX-TV & WPSU-FM Radio Interviews, re: Penn State Forum Topics & John Roberts, October 17, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 17)
      - 3rd Annual Tony Coelho Lecture in Disability Employment Law and Policy: New York Law School; Speech "Making Disability Pay", October 19, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 18)
      - Breakfast Fundraiser for Jane Ervin, Lehigh County Executive Candidate, October 24, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 19)
      - Dinner with Charles and Alison Skene, October 24, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 20)
      - Congressional Briefing, re: Homeland Security Regional Initiatives (ASME Innovative Technologies Inst.), October 27, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 21)
      - General Counsel Academy in NYC, Harold Pratt Mansion, November 3, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 22)
      - 18th Judicial Conference; Speech "Homeland Security, Civil Liberties and the Rule of Law", November 4, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 23)
      - Meeting with Michael Kramer, re: United Nations, November 14, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 24)
      - US Sentencing Commission Public Meeting: Statement, re: Chapter Eight Waiver of Attorney-Client Privilege & Work Product Protections, November 15, 2005 (Box 1064, Folder 25)